http://www.bioversityinternational.org/privacy-policy/

HomeAbout usWho we areHistoryAllianceAnnual ReportFinancial StatementsStaff biosLatest NewsDirector General BlogNewsletterMediaNewsKey eventsA taste of biodiversityConvention on Biological DiversityWhere we workCentral and South AmericaPeruWest and Central AfricaEast and Southern AfricaEthiopiaKenyaUgandaCentral and South AsiaIndiaSouth-east AsiaChinaGovernanceDirector General OfficeBoard of TrusteesBioversity International UKBioversity International USA, IncOpportunitiesJob vacanciesWhat we offerInternationally recruited staffLocally recruited staffWork environmentProfessional staffSupport staffJunior Professional OfficersHonorary research fellows & visiting researchersShort-term assignmentsFellowshipsInternshipsContact usInternal staff areaInnovationsThe Agrobiodiversity IndexWhat is agrobiodiversity?Seeds for NeedsAdapting to climate changeSeed System DiversityCrowdsourcingImpactResourcesPartnersTrees for SeedsResearchAgricultural biodiversitySustainable development goalsInitiativesHealthy dietsFarms, forests, landscapesGenetic resourcesResearch portfolioAdaptation to climate changeSeeds for NeedsAgricultural ecosystemsPests and diseasesLandscapes and ecosystemsIntegrating wild and agricultural biodiversityGlobally important agricultural heritage systems (GIAHS)Banana genetic resources and management systemsBananas for nutritionInternational Musa Germplasm Transit CentrePlant genomics and bioinformaticsConservation of crop diversityManaging crop diversity on farmCrop wild relativesCommunity seedbanksEconomicsDiet diversityImproving nutrition with diverse local foodsVitamin A-rich bananasBiodiversity for food and nutritionRural to urban agri-food chainsForest and tree diversitySafeguarding Forest DiversitySustainable use of forest diversityForest RestorationTrees for nutritionWhy forest and tree genetic diversity mattersFruit tree and tree crop diversityTropical fruit treesCentral Asia fruit treesCacaoCoconutMarkets for diverse speciesMilletsAndean grainsAfrican leafy vegetablesChilli peppersPolicies for plant diversity managementMutual implementation of Nagoya Protocol and Plant TreatyFarmer Variety approved NepalCross-cutting themesGender at the centre of our researchGender in seed systems and plant breedingGender-responsive forestry researchStructuring research for impactPreparing the ground for impactful researchUsing ontologies to harness research dataUnderstanding and increasing the impact of researchAlliance's response to COVID-19e-LibraryPublicationsSearch the e-libraryMainstreaming Agrobiodiversity in Sustainable Food SystemIssues in agricultural biodiversityTraining materialsDescriptorsImpact briefsABD Index ReportCelebrating 45 Years of Agrobiodiversity ResearchAnnual ReportsAnnual report 2019Annual Report 2018Annual Report 2017Annual Report 2016Annual Report 2015Annual Report 20142014 – An overviewResearch highlightsPublication highlightsResearch partnersFunding partnersFinancial informationForewordDatabasesCollecting missionsSearch Collecting missions databaseHistoryNew World FruitsSearch New World Fruits DatabaseTips on searchingHow to contributeMultimedia libraryVideosImagesInfographicsLibrary Services and Knowledge ManagementOpen Access at Bioversity InternationalThe Bioversity International Herbarium ProjectPlant Genetic Resources NewsletterPartnersResearch partnersCGIAR partnershipResearch partner listFunding partnersFunding partner listHow we are fundedGet involvedA good investmentBioversity International and CGIARBioversity International and the European UnionBioversity International and ItalySkip to main contentYou are here:HomePrivacy policy & cookiesPrivacy policy & cookiesBioversity International (also known as IPGRI) (effective as of December 19th, 2012)This privacy notice tells you about the information we collect from you when you use our website. In collecting this information, we are acting as a data controller and, by law, we are required to provide you with information about us, about why and how we use your data, and about the rights you have over your data.Who we areWe are Bioversity International. Our address is Via dei Tre Denari 472/a, 00054, Fiumicino, Rome, Italy. You can contact us by post at the above address or by email at bioversity-ds-requests@cgiar.org.We are not required to have a data protection officer, so any enquiries about our use of your personal data should be addressed to the contact details above.When you use our websiteWhen you use our website a number of cookies are used by us and by third parties to allow the website to function, to collect useful information about visitors and improving your user experience.Your rights as a data subjectBy law, you can ask us what information we hold about you, and you can ask us to correct it if it is inaccurate. If we have asked for your consent to process your personal data, you may withdraw that consent at any time.To submit a request regarding your personal data by email or post, please use the contact information provided above in the Who Are We section of this policy.Your right to complainIf you have a complaint about our use of your information, we would prefer you to contact us directly in the first instance so that we can address your complaint. However, you can also contact the Italian Data Protection Authority via their website at https://www.garanteprivacy.it/web/guest/home_en or write to them at:Piazza di Monte Citorio, 121 – 00186 Roma, ItalyUpdates to this privacy policyWe regularly review and, if appropriate, update this privacy policy as our services and use of personal data evolves. If we want to make use of your personal data in a way that we haven’t previously identified, we will contact you to provide information about this and ask for your consent.We will update the version number and date of this document each time it is changed.What are cookies and how and why we use them?What are cookies?A cookie is a small text file that a website saves on your computer or mobile device when you visit the site. It enables the website to remember your actions and preferences (such as language, font size and other display preferences) over a period of time, in order to keep the same settings whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another.Cookie analysis and performance.Cookies are used to collect and analyze traffic and use the site anonymously. These cookies, even without identifying the user, allow, for example, detecting if the same user returns at different times. They also allow monitoring the system to improve performance and usability.Third Party CookiesUsers of our web site may receive cookies from the main site ("first party"), and/or from websites maintained by other organizations ("third party").Social Plugins CookiesIn our site, we use "social plugins" for Facebook, Twitter and Google+. The most common use of these social plugins is to share content on social networks. They also transmit cookies to and from our site to the third party service. To know more about the information collected by "third parties" used please go to: Facebook information: https://www.facebook.com/help/cookies/ Facebook (setting): log into your account > Section privacy.Twitter information: https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170514 Twitter (setting): https://twitter.com/settings/securityGoogle+ information: http://www.google.it/intl/en/policies/technologies/cookies/ Google+ (setting): http://www.google.it/intl/it/policies/technologies/managing/Google Analytics CookiesThis site does not use Google analysis tools to track or collect personally identifiable information. For more information, please go to https://www.google.it/policies/privacy/partners/You can selectively disable the action of installing Google Analytics on your browser component of the opt-out provided by Google. To disable the action of Google Analytics, please go to https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptoutOther third party cookiesIn addition to the above listed cookies users of our web site may receive also cookies from the following services:Pingdom https://www.pingdom.com/legal/privacy-policyGoogle Translate http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/AddThis http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policyYouTube http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/How to control cookies?You can control and/or delete cookies as you wish – for details, see aboutcookies.org. You can delete all cookies that are already on your computer and you can set most browsers to prevent them from being placed. If you do this, however, you may have to manually adjust some preferences every time you visit a site and some services and functionalities may not work.Disabling "third party" cookies will not decrease web site usability. Each web site or application can have its own cookie settings. Furthermore the best browsers allow defining different settings for cookies "first party" and "third party". For example, in Firefox through the menu Tools-> Options -> Privacy, you can access a control panel where you can specify whether or not to accept the different types of cookies and remove them.Chrome: https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=enFirefox: https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/cookies-information-websites-store-on-your-computerInternet Explorer: http://windows.microsoft.com/it-it/windows7/how-to-manage-cookies-in-internet-explorer-11Opera: http://help.opera.com/Windows/10.00/it/cookies.htmlSafari: https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT201265 Last updated: 15 May 2019
